Ima Hogg Symphony Programs Collection
University of Houston Libraries
- Programs (Box 3-6)
  - Various European Theatres, 1963 - 1967 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Various European Theatres, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Various European Theatres, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Various European Theatres, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Various European Theatres, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Various European Theatres, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 44-45)
  - Various European Theatres, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 46-47)
  - Various European Theatres, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 48-49)
  - Various European Theatres, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 50-51)
  - Various European Theatres, undated (Box 6, Folder 52-55)
  - Travel Itinerary and Memorabilia (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Miscellaneous Articles (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Clippings (Box 7-9)
  Newspaper clippings primarily concerning the Houston Symphony Orchestra, the Houston Symphony Society, and Ima Hogg and the Hogg family. The original clippings have been replaced by photocopies on acid-free paper for preservation purposes. The clippings are arranged chronologically from earliest to most recent.
  - Clippings, 1915, 1931, 1936, 1937, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1940, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 6-7)
  - Clippings, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 8-11)
  - Clippings, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 12-20)
  - Clippings, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 1-4)
  - Clippings, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
  - Clippings, 1958, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1960, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1961, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
  - Clippings, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 12-14)
  - Clippings, 1964, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 9, Folder 1-11)